konoozi.com 2015-06-04

# Privacy Policy

Rating: 0.0/ **5** (0 votes cast)

 **General**  
Konoozi LLC (“Company” or “we” or “us” or “our”) respects the privacy of its users (“user” or “you”) of our website ([www.konoozi.com](http://www.konoozi.com/))

Konoozi LLC company privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) is designed to inform you, as a user of the website, about the types of information that we may gather about or collect from you in connection with your use of the website. It also is intended to explain the conditions under which Konoozi uses and discloses that information, and your rights in relation to that information.

 **Web Cookie**  
Konoozi LLC may use “Web cookie” to personalize and/or enhance your user experience. A cookie is a small digital file with unique identification that is stored on user’s computer by a webpage server. Web Cookies cannot be used to run programs on or deliver viruses to your computer. Web Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a webserver in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Konoozi LLC uses cookies on the Website to keep track of services you have used, to record your provided name and email address or any user preferences. Konoozi may also uses Web Cookies to track the pages that users visit during each Website session, both to help Konoozi improve users’ experiences and to help us understand how the website is being used. KONOOZI LLC USERS WHO DO NOT WISH TO HAVE WEB COOKIES PLACED ON THEIR COMPUTERS SHOULD SET THEIR BROWSERS TO REFUSE WEB COOKIES BEFORE ACCESSING THE WEBSITE, WITH THE UNDERSTANDING THAT CERTAIN FEATURES OF THE WEBSITE MAY NOT FUNCTION PROPERLY WITHOUT THE AID OF WEB COOKIES. WEBSITE USERS WHO REFUSE WEB COOKIES ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY RESULTING LOSS OF FUNCTIONALITY.

 **Children**  
The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) protects the online privacy of children under 13 years of age. Konoozi LLC does not knowingly collect or maintain personal information from anyone under the age of 13, unless or except as permitted by law. Any person who provides personal information through the website represents to us that he or she is 13 years of age or older. If we learn that personal information has been collected from a user under 13 years of age on or through the Website, we will take the appropriate steps to delete all related information. The parent or legal guardian of a child under 13, who has become a member of the Website or has otherwise transferred personal information to the Website, please [contact](http://www.konoozi.com/contact-us/ "contact") Company using our contact information below to have that child’s account terminated and information deleted.

 **Information we gather**  
The following information is gathered from Konoozi LLC website visitors:

  * IP address

 **How we use the information we gather**  
Konoozi LLC uses the information to enhance our visitor experience and better services to all of our users. When you contact Konoozi, we may keep a record of your communication to help solve any issues you might be facing. We may use your email address to inform you about the ongoing issues updates, and our services, such as letting you know about upcoming changes or improvements.

We will ask for your consent before using information for a purpose other than those that are set out in this Privacy Policy.

Konoozi processes personal information on our servers in many countries around the world. We may process your personal information on a server located outside the country where you live.

 **The people that are given access to this information**  
We restrict access to personal information to Konoozi employees, contractors and agents who “need” to know that information in order to process it for us, and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations.

 **The security measures we have in place to protect your personal information**  
Your privacy matters to Konoozi. To safeguard your personal information, we work hard to protect Konoozi and our users from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of information we hold. In particular:

• We make use of SSL technology to encrypting many of our services.

• We review our processes for information collection, storage and data processing practices, including security measures to guard against unauthorized access to data systems.

• We restrict access to personal information to Konoozi employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for us, and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.

Your browser settings may allow you to block these cookies, however website owners recommend visitors have them enabled to help us personalize visitors’ experience to their website.

Additionally, third-party advertisers on the websites may use cookies for tracking purposes.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on their visit to sites they visit on the Internet.

Website visitors may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. Also, you can learn more about other ad-serving companies and opt out from their use of cookies<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> at the NAI website. Network Advertising Initiative<http://www.networkadvertising.org/> (NAI) is a committee to building responsible advertising policies across the Internet.

 **Enforcement**  
We regularly review our compliance with our Privacy Policy. Konoozi complies with the US-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the US-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, storage and processing of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. ****

Contact  
If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact our privacy officer at:  
Privacy Officer  
Konoozi LLC  
Buffalo, NY 14210  
Email: [support@konoozi.com](mailto:support@konoozi.com)  
Phone: (716) 652-5676
